[jazz music]
[爵士乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Wow,
I never thought The Low Tides
哇，
我从没想过低潮
would come to a backwater town
like Bikini Bottom.
会来到一个死水小镇
比如比基尼泳裤。
Squidward, I didn't know
you liked The Low Tides!
章鱼哥，我不知道
你喜欢《低潮》！
[grunting, groaning]
[咕哝，呻吟]
Yeah, they're fine,
是的，他们很好，
but that Clair St. Claire
is the real talent!
但那个克莱尔·圣克莱尔
才是真正的人才！
They say his clarinet
is so fancy,
他们说他的单簧管
是如此奇特，
it doesn't play any wrong notes!
它不会演奏任何错误的音符！
All right, enough nonsense!
Listen up!
好了，废话够多了！
听着！
This here's the biggest concert
这是最大的音乐会
to come to Bikini Bottom
in decades!
来到比基尼堡
几十年后！
[sniffs]
[嗅嗅]
You smell that, boyos?
你闻到了吗，男孩？
[sniffs]
[嗅嗅]
Ooh!
[giggles]
哦！
[咯咯笑]
You smell like corn chips,
Mr. Krabs!
你闻起来像玉米片
蟹老板！
I just smell the toilets.
我只是闻到厕所的味道。
[flush]
- Phew!
[冲水]
- 唷！
Yeah, yeah.
All that's in the air too,
是啊是啊。
一切也都在空气中，
along with the smell of money!
伴随着金钱的味道！
The show is sold out,
演出已售罄，
which means there's
30,000 fans in there.
这意味着有
那里有30,000名粉丝。
And you are gonna sell
a Krabby patty
你要卖掉
蟹肉饼
to every single one of them!
致他们每一位！
[gasps]
[喘气]
What a great way
to make 30,000 new friends,
多么好的方法啊
结交30,000个新朋友，
don't ya think Squidward, huh?
你不觉得是章鱼哥吗？
Hmm?
唔？
Don't you?
- [groans]
不是吗？
- [呻吟]
And what are you going to do
while we work all day?
你打算做什么
当我们整天工作的时候？
Glad you asked,
Mr. Squidward.
很高兴你问，
章鱼哥先生。
I will be taking
the toughest job of all.
我将采取
最艰难的工作。
I'll be sneaking onstage
我会偷偷地登上舞台
to unfurl this here banner
behind the band.
在此展开此横幅
在乐队后面。
[mimics fanfare]
[模仿大张旗鼓]
"The Krusty Krab.
“蟹堡王。
"Krabby patties are yummy.
Please your face.
“蟹肉饼很好吃。
请你的脸。
Tonight would be great."
今晚会很棒。”
That's the worst advertisement
I've ever seen.
这才是最烂的广告
我曾经见过。
[groans]
[呻吟]
What do you know about
celebrity endorser-mints?
你知道什么
名人代言薄荷糖？
Just get in there
and sell me patties!
只要进去
还卖给我肉饼！
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
走，走，走，走，走，走，走！
[audience clamoring]
[观众叫嚷]
Oh, boy!
哦，孩子！
SpongeBob and Squidward,
working side by side!
海绵宝宝和章鱼哥，
并肩工作！
The two amigos, patty purveyors,
这两个朋友，肉饼供应商，
the delicious duo.
美味的二人组。
Backstage, huh?
后台吧？
[moans, clamoring]
[呻吟，叫喊]
Mr. Squidward,
you're on in two minutes!
章鱼哥先生，
两分钟后你就开始了！
[groans]
Mm-hmm.
[呻吟]
嗯嗯。
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's The Low Tides
女士们、先生们，
这是低潮
with their special guest,
Squidward Tentacles!
和他们的特邀嘉宾，
章鱼哥的触手！
[cheers]
[干杯]
[big band music]
[大乐队音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[clarinet plays]
[单簧管演奏]
♪ ♪
♪♪
all: Squidward,
Squidward, Squidward!
全部： 章鱼哥，
章鱼哥，章鱼哥！
♪ ♪
♪♪
Hmm.
Huh?
唔。
啊？
Concession Kings!
Bun buddies forever!
优惠之王！
永远的包子朋友！
- [groans]
- Whoa!
- [呻吟]
- 哇！
You know, SpongeBob,
we would cover more ground
你知道，海绵宝宝，
我们将覆盖更多领域
if we split up.
如果我们分手了。
Why don't you sell
to that half of the audience,
你为什么不卖
对那一半观众来说
and I'll take this half!
这一半我来拿！
Mmm, well, I was looking forward
嗯，嗯，我很期待
to spending
the whole day with you.
支出
和你在一起一整天。
I know, I'm so disappointed.
我知道，我很失望。
But that is a great idea,
Squidward!
但这是个好主意
章鱼哥！
I love how you always put
the Krusty Krabs's needs
我喜欢你总是这样放
蟹堡王的需求
before your own.
在你自己之前。
[laughs]
[笑]
Yes, I do, don't I?
[chuckles]
是的，我愿意，不是吗？
[笑声]
Zip!
拉链！
[hums, strains]
[嗡嗡声，张力]
Krabby patties!
蟹肉饼！
Get your fresh,
hot patties here!
让你的新鲜，
这里有热肉饼！
I'll take a Krabby Patty!
我要吃蟹肉饼！
Coming right up!
马上就来了！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Ooh!
- Watch it!
- 哦！
- 注意！
Your patty, sir!
先生，你的小馅饼！
Hey, Snack Boy!
嘿，小吃男孩！
Krabby patty me!
蟹肉饼我！
- Yo!
- What?
- 哟！
- 什么？
Hmm?
唔？
Hey, can I get
some mustard here?
嘿，我可以得到吗
这里有芥末吗？
Mustard for the mister!
You got it!
给先生加芥末！
你明白了！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
all: Whoa!
全体：哇！
[squeals]
Thanks, kiddo!
[尖叫声]
谢谢你，孩子！
all: Huh?
全体：啊？
[laughter]
[笑声]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
Hmm?
唔？
Easy as taking money
from a baby.
拿钱一样容易
来自一个婴儿。
[strains]
[菌株]
No fans on the stage.
Get back to your seat!
舞台上没有粉丝。
回到你的座位上！
[Tommy Walker's "Charge"]
[汤米·沃克的“冲锋”]
Whoa!
哇！
[laughter, groaning]
[笑声、呻吟]
Whoa!
哇！
Oh, man, I still can't
believe your uncle Fred
哦，伙计，我还是不能
相信你叔叔弗雷德
was able to get us
backstage passes.
能够找到我们
后台通行证。
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
Now, if I can just find
Clair St. Claire.
现在，如果我能找到
克莱尔·圣克莱尔。
Oh, I'm sure he'd let
a fellow Gob Stick aficionado
哦，我确信他会让
Gob Stick 爱好者
play his instrument.
演奏他的乐器。
Hmm?
唔？
Oh, excuse me, janitor,
哦，对不起，清洁工，
do you know where
the green room is?
你知道在哪里吗
绿色房间是？
That depends.
Where's your backstage pass?
这要看情况。
你的后台通行证在哪里？
[whimpering]
Oh, uh, it's right...
[呜咽]
哦哦，原来如此……
Huh?
Ooh!
啊？
哦！
[cheers]
[干杯]
He's in the band!
他在乐队里！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Huh?
啊？
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[groans]
[呻吟]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
Oh, this must be it!
噢，一定是这个！
Okay.
[clears throat]
好的。
[清嗓子]
Clair St. Claire?
It is I, Squid... Patrick?
克莱尔圣克莱尔？
是我，乌贼……帕特里克？
Sorry, I don't know anyone
named SquidPatrick.
抱歉，我谁也不认识
名叫乌贼帕特里克。
Patrick you idiot,
what are you doing here?
帕特里克你这个白痴
你在这里做什么？
This is my room.
这是我的房间。
Did you not see the star
on the door?
你没看到星星吗
在门上？
[groans]
Well, where's the green room?
[呻吟]
那么，绿色房间在哪里？
I'm trying to find the band!
- I don't know.
我正在努力寻找乐队！
- 我不知道。
Hey,
I'll bet my friend Stan does.
嘿，
我敢打赌我的朋友斯坦会的。
Yo, Stan!
哟，斯坦！
[footsteps pounding, yells]
[脚步声重重，喊叫]
You...
你...
Hey Stan, hey,
could you show my friend
嘿斯坦，嘿，
你可以给我朋友看吗
where the green room is?
绿色房间在哪里？
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of him.
不用担心。
我会好好照顾他的。
- [groans]
- [laughs]
- [呻吟]
- [笑]
Help me.
帮我。
Bye, SquidPatrick!
Have fun!
再见，乌贼帕特里克！
玩得开心！
[gulping]
[吞咽]
Hey, where's my patty?
嘿，我的馅饼在哪里？
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Yeah, over here!
- I want one!
- 是的，在这里！
- 我想要一个！
I'm a patty launching machine!
我是肉饼发射机！
[laughs]
[笑]
Thank you, Patty Boy!
谢谢你，帕蒂男孩！
It was nothing.
没什么。
Nothing!
I'm out of patties!
没有什么！
我的肉饼没了！
Well, I guess I just better
make some more!
嗯，我想我只是更好
多做一些！
Yup!
是的！
[hums]
[哼哼]
- Huh?
- [hums]
- 啊？
- [哼哼]
[hums]
[哼哼]
Fresh hot Krabby patties here!
新鲜热腾腾的蟹肉饼来啦！
Put a patty in your pie hole!
在你的馅饼洞里放一块肉饼！
Huh?
啊？
Ah!
啊!
Oh, it looks like I fed
my entire section.
哦，看来我吃饱了
我的整个部分。
Hmm?
唔？
[moans, groans]
[呻吟，呻吟]
[stomach rumbles]
[肚子咕咕叫]
[moans, groans]
[呻吟，呻吟]
Well, I guess Squidward
wouldn't mind
嗯，我猜章鱼哥
不介意
if I sell a few patties
in his section.
如果我卖一些肉饼
在他的部分。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
They'll never look
for me up here.
他们永远不会看
对我来说。
Hmm.
唔。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[audience cheers]
[观众欢呼]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
[clamoring]
[叫喊]
Oh!
Whoa!
哦！
哇！
Oh!
哦！
Whoa!
哇！
[cheers]
[干杯]
Eww!
Yuck!
哇！
哎呀！
Whoa!
No, no, wait!
哇！
不不不，等等！
[yells, groans]
[尖叫声、呻吟声]
Oh...
哦...
[spits]
[吐口水]
Yuck!
哎呀！
Who eats yogurt at
a rock concert?
谁在吃酸奶
摇滚音乐会？
All right, where am... [gasps]
好吧，我在哪里...[喘气]
The stage!
舞台！
Oh, forget the green room!
哦，忘了绿色房间吧！
That's Clair St. Claire's
clarinet!
那是克莱尔·圣克莱尔
单簧管！
[chuckles]
[笑声]
Ladies and gentlefish,
polyps and fries!
女士们，温柔的鱼，
息肉和薯条！
Here's the band you've
all been waiting for!
这是你的乐队
大家都在等待！
You know them!
You love them!
你认识他们！
你爱他们！
It's The Low Tides!
退潮了！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
Huh?
[yells]
啊？
[喊叫]
[whines]
[哀鸣]
[groans]
Oh, oh, oh!
[呻吟]
哦，哦，哦！
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
噢，噢，噢，噢。
[cheers]
[干杯]
[jazz music]
[爵士乐]
[piano plays]
[钢琴演奏]
♪ I was a lonely,
lonely lad ♪
♪ 我是一个孤独的人，
孤独的小伙子♪
♪ Solitary soul ♪
♪ 孤独的灵魂 ♪
♪ Didn't have the rock ♪
♪ 没有石头 ♪
♪ And I didn't know
how to roll ♪
♪ 我不知道
怎么滚♪
♪ Joined me a band,
singing on the stage ♪
♪ 加入了我的乐队，
在舞台上唱歌♪
♪ They was swooning
and a-screaming ♪
♪ 他们神魂颠倒
还有尖叫声♪
♪ And now I'm all the rage ♪
♪ 现在我很愤怒 ♪
♪ It's a feeding frenzy ♪
♪ 这是一场疯狂的喂食 ♪
♪ Everybody wants
a piece of me ♪
♪ 每个人都想要
我的一部分♪
♪ It's a feeding frenzy ♪
♪ 这是一场疯狂的喂食 ♪
♪ I can't get me no privacy ♪
♪ 我不能让自己没有隐私 ♪
♪ How am I gonna shake 'em? ♪
- Is it really him?
♪ 我该如何摇动他们？ ♪
- 真的是他吗？
♪ The freaky fans found me ♪
♪ 奇怪的粉丝找到了我 ♪
♪ Man, they'll tear me
limb from limb ♪
♪ 老兄，他们会撕裂我
肢体与肢体 ♪
♪ They claw at my clothes,
steal my shoes ♪
♪ 他们抓我的衣服，
偷我的鞋♪
♪ Tear out my hair,
I got nothing left to lose ♪
♪ 扯掉我的头发，
我已经没有什么可失去的了♪
♪ Oh, it's a feeding frenzy ♪
♪ 噢，这是一场疯狂的喂食 ♪
♪ The kids can't get enough ♪
♪ 孩子们还不够 ♪
♪ Oh, it's a feeding frenzy ♪
♪ 噢，这是一场疯狂的喂食 ♪
♪ This rock-n-roll
is getting rough ♪
♪ 这首摇滚乐
变得粗暴了♪
[clarinet plays]
[单簧管演奏]
[groans]
[呻吟]
Oh.
哦。
Buddy, could you
put down your phone?
伙计，你可以吗
放下你的手机吗？
You're blocking my shot!
你挡住了我的射击！
♪ ♪
Ah, looks like everyone
has a patty.
啊，看来大家都一样
有一个肉饼。
[burps]
[打嗝]
- [yells]
- Ow, ow.
- [大喊]
- 噢，噢。
Everyone but the band!
除了乐队以外的所有人！
[whines]
[哀鸣]
Hmm.
Oh!
唔。
哦！
Aha!
啊哈！
Must sell patties!
一定要卖肉饼！
[beep, whirr]
[嘟嘟声、呼呼声]
[strains]
[菌株]
Huh?
啊？
Oh!
Whoa!
哦！
哇！
- Ugh!
- Whoa!
- 呃！
- 哇！
[yells]
[喊叫]
Whoa!
哇！
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
There's no stopping me
this time!
没有人能阻止我
这次！
Here we go!
开始了！
A-one, a-two.
[beep]
A-一，A-二。
[嘟]
Huh?
Hey!
啊？
嘿！
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
Help!
[garbled speech]
帮助！
[乱码言论]
[yells]
[喊叫]
[sighs]
Huh?
[叹气]
啊？
Special delivery
for The Low Tides!
特快专递
为了低潮！
Huh?
Whoa!
啊？
哇！
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜。
Oh!
Hey!
哦！
嘿！
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
- [yells]
- [whimpers]
- [大喊]
- [呜咽]
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜。
Come on!
快点！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[groans]
[呻吟]
Don't forget!
别忘了！
Brought to you
by the Krusty Krab!
给你带来了
蟹堡王！
The Krusty Krab.
A crummy place to eat?
蟹堡王。
吃饭的地方很糟糕吗？
I didn't know they
were serving us crummy food!
我不知道他们
为我们提供了糟糕的食物！
Huh?
[groans]
啊？
[呻吟]
Oh, come on.
[chuckles]
哦，来吧。
[笑声]
Boo!
Boo I say!
嘘！
我说嘘！
[booing]
- Hey, no, no, no!
[嘘声]
- 嘿，不，不，不！
You don't understand!
你不明白！
It's not crummy!
[groans]
这并不糟糕！
[呻吟]
It's yummy!
It's... it's...
真好吃！
这是……这是……
[booing]
[嘘声]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
[clicking rhythmically]
- Boo!
[有节奏的点击声]
- 嘘！
Ooh, that's a hot beat,
Mr. Krabs!
哦哦，这节奏太火爆了
蟹老板！
[nose flute plays]
[鼻笛演奏]
♪ ♪
Oh, they're pretty good!
哦，他们很不错！
Yeah!
Let's give them a chance!
是的！
让我们给他们一个机会吧！
♪ ♪
All right, now for a little
licorice stick!
好吧，现在稍微
甘草棒！
[inhales]
[吸气]
Squidward's got a clarinet!
Run!
章鱼哥有一支单簧管！
跑步！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
[clarinet plays]
[单簧管演奏]
♪ ♪
I can't believe it!
我简直不敢相信！
This really is the greatest
clarinet ever made!
这确实是最伟大的
单簧管曾经制作过！
And you're the greatest
audience I've ever... oh!
而你是最伟大的
我曾经的观众...哦！
[crickets chirp]
[蟋蟀鸣叫]
[groans]
[呻吟]
Huh?
啊？
Nice jam, baby.
美味的果酱，宝贝。
Validation?
验证？
Oh, thank you,
Clair St. Claire!
哦，谢谢你，
克莱尔圣克莱尔！
Oh, this is the best day
of my life!
哦，这是最好的一天
我的生活！
I can die happy!
我可以快乐地死去！
[sighs]
[叹气]
Oh, no, you don't!
哦，不，你不！
You're working tonight,
and corpses can't collect cash!
今晚你还要工作，
而且尸体不能收取现金！
[groans]
[呻吟]
Well, still the best day
of my life.
嗯，仍然是最好的一天
我的生活。